<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CollapsingToolbarLayout</string>

    <string name="nested_scroll_view_text">
        For over a decade after the release Half-Life 2: Episode Two in October 2007, there was very little news from Valve on the next Half-Life game. Half-Life 2: Episode Three, the third and final installment of the Half-Life 2 episodes, was expected to follow soon after Episode Two, as Valve had stated that they aimed to release a new episode every six to eight months. However, as of April 2022, three pieces of concept art are all Valve have shown of the sequel. Since then, Valve has released ten other games. On November 18, 2019, 12 years after the release of Half-Life 2: Episode Two and the day before the 21st anniversary of the release of the original Half-Life, Valve announced Half-Life: Alyx, a virtual reality video game set in the Half-Life universe, where you play as Alyx Vance in the aftermath of the Combine invasion on earth, before the events of Half-Life 2. On November 21 the first trailer for the game was released and the game became available for pre-purchase. According to lead programmer David Speyrer, in an interview with the video game magazine The Verge released the same day, Half-Life: Alyx is "the next part of the Half-Life story," and says that they recommend playing through Half-Life 2: Episode Two beforehand. Prior to Alyx\'s announcement, leaks suggest that Valve abandoned the episodic model and was working on a full sequel entitled Half-Life 3, but Valve employees consistently refused to comment on the status or nature of the next Half-Life game, much to the displeasure of their fanbase. Despite general satisfaction with the games Valve has made since Episode Two, the Half-Life 3 continues to be their most anticipated title, and since the long-awaited release of Duke Nukem Forever in 2011, it has become gaming\'s most infamous case of continuing vaporware. In an interview with Geoff Keighley (author of The Final Hours of Portal 2 and The Final Hours of Half-Life 2), Half-Life: Alyx\'s developers remained coy on the subject of whether Half-Life: Alyx could bridge the gap towards a virtual reality-based Half-Life 3, noting they would have to see how Half-Life: Alyx was received. It\'s amazing that after the series had lain dormant for so long, Half-Life fans were still scrambling for another release. While 2020\'s VR title Half-Life: Alyx was a prequel rather than the full sequel that many were hoping for, it has rekindled some hope and marked the end of a drought. In an interview with GameInformer, Valve\'s Robin Walker said that Alyx is "not the end" for the franchise while writer Eric Wolpaw said in an interview with PCGamer that he\'s "ready to sign up for the next one". So, at the very least we know the series isn\'t retiring but we still don\'t know whether its next release will be Half-Life 3, another VR title related to Half-Life Alyx or something else completely fresh in the same universe. Hopefully we won\'t have to wait quite as long to find out.
    </string>
</resources>